Contact

3138 Long Bough Ct. Houston, TX 77059 7138175294 (Mobile) josephinehoang2010@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/josephine-hoang-88352888 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Word PowerPoint

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

PeriOp 101 Registered Nurse Registered Nurse

Josephine Hoang

Travel Operating Room Nurse

Houston, Texas

Summary

I am a registered nurse with a RN license to practice in the states of Texas and Washington as well as compact states. I graduated with my Bachelor of Science in Nursing from Texas A&M University: Health Science Center -College Station, TX, in 2015. I have clinical experience in specialized surgery in both inpatient and outpatient environments including general surgery, orthopedics, ENT, plastic, pain management, and others.

Experience

Aya Healthcare 9 months

Travel OR RN Circulator February 2020 - Present (5 months) Billings, Montana Area

Travel OR RN Circulator at outpatient surgery center with specialties including general, ENT, pediatrics, urology, GYN, orthopedics, podiatry, eyes, pain management, and others.

Travel OR RN Circulator October 2019 - January 2020 (4 months)

Yakima, Washington Area

Traveling operating room nurse at inpatient community hospital with surgical specialties of orthopedics, robotics, general, GYN, neuro, endoscopy, and trauma.

Nobilis Health Corp.
OR RN Circulator
March 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 7 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Outpatient surgery center specialized in ear, nose, and throat (ENT), orthopedics (sports medicine), and general surgery (hernia).

Roles include OR RN circulator, intraoperative patient care, medical and pharmaceutical supply management, maintaining sterile field, and

collaboration with pre-op/PACU nurses, surgeons, anesthesiologists, and operative team.

Memorial Hermann Health System RN II- Operating Room Nurse February 2016 - February 2018 (2 years 1 month)

Inpatient clinical experience as an OR circulator in specialized surgery including ear, nose and throat (ENT), general surgery, pain management, orthopedic, plastic surgery, and others.

Completion of PeriOp 101 course and one year nursing residency program. Member of Magnet Committee at current hospital.

Participation in precepting nursing residency interns in the OR. Laser safety officer.

Collaboration with ENT coordinator and medical reps towards growth of ENT specialty.

Texas A&M University
Student Nurse
August 2013 - March 2015 (1 year 8 months)
Bryan/College Station, Texas Area

I have gained extensive experience in clinical rotations in settings such as pediatric and adult critical care, medical/surgical, and telemetry units at local facilities as a student nurse under the supervision of a RN preceptor or faculty instructor. Hospitals I have done clinical rotations for are local hospitals in the College Station/Bryan area as well as McLane's Children's Hospital and the VA Hospital in Temple, TX. I provided patient-centered care through critical-thinking, assessment, planning, implementing, and evaluation of outcomes.

Education

Texas A&M University System Health Science Center Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

University of Houston Nutrition/Kinesiology · (2010 - 2013)